const data = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "In which year was The Godfather first released?",
    incorrect: ["1988", "1990", "1971"],
    correct: "1972"
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "In which 1963 classic film did Charles Bronson appear?",
    incorrect: ["Family of Cops", "The Sea Wolf", "Red Sun"],
    correct: "The Great Escape"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Which film starring Chris Hemsworth and Daniel Brühl, charts the Formula 1 rivalry of James Hunt and Niki Lauda?",
    incorrect: ["Spiderhead", "Extraction", "Blackhat"],
    correct: "Rush"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Which actor provided the voice for the character Nemo in the 2003 film Finding Nemo?",
    incorrect: ["Jason Statham", "Chris Evans", "Mark Ruffalo"],
    correct: "Alexander Gould"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which actress played Mary Poppins in the 1964 film Mary Poppins?",
    incorrect: ["Emily Blunt", "Julia Roberts", "Margot Robbie"],
    correct: "Julie Andrews"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Which prisoner dubbed ‘the most violent prisoner in Britain’ was the subject of a 2009 film?",
    incorrect: ["Chris Hemsworth", "Christian Bale", "Heath Ledger"],
    correct: "Charles Bronson"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What 2008 film starring Chritian Bale has this quote: “I believe whatever doesn’t kill you, simply makes you…stranger.”?",
    incorrect: ["The Pale Blue Eyes", "The Big Short", "The Prestige"],
    correct: "The Dark Knight"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Which British action actor played the part of Lee Christmas alongside Sylvester Stallone in the film The Expendables?",
    incorrect: ["Henry Cavill", "Tom Holland", "Tom Hiddleston"],
    correct: "Jason Statham"
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "How many self-referential cameos did Alfred Hitchcock make in his films from 1927-1976 – 33, 35 or 37?",
    incorrect: ["35"],
    correct: "37"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Which 1982 film was greatly accepted by film fans for its portrayal of the love between a young, fatherless suburban boy and a lost, benevolent and homesick visitor from another planet?",
    incorrect: ["Prometheus", "Alien vs Predator", "Alien: Covenant"],
    correct: "E.T. The Extra-Terrestrial"
  }
];

export default data;